{
    "subject": "resource/X-treme_Close-Up",
    "predicate": "property/type",
    "object": "video",
    "human_readable": "The type of X-treme Close-Up is a video.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9750851988792419,
            "question": "Is an X-treme Close-Up a form of video?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9046112895011902,
            "question": "What makes an X-treme Close-Up distinct from other types of videos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8044652938842773,
            "question": "What type of media is an X-treme Close-Up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7973703742027283,
            "question": "What is the purpose of using an X-treme Close-Up in filmmaking or video production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7580956220626831,
            "question": "How has the use of X-treme Close-Ups evolved over time in video production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7096241116523743,
            "question": "What are some technical aspects to consider when filming an X-treme Close-Up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6530609726905823,
            "question": "Can you describe what an X-treme Close-Up typically shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6389644145965576,
            "question": "Are there different subgenres within X-treme Close-Ups?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5447419881820679,
            "question": "Can you give examples of situations where an X-treme Close-Up might be used effectively?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5357221364974976,
            "question": "How does an X-treme Close-Up affect the viewer's emotional response?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The type of X-treme Close-Up is a video.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2782_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give examples of situations where an X-treme Close-Up might be used effectively?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2782_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there different subgenres within X-treme Close-Ups?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2782_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe what an X-treme Close-Up typically shows?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2782_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2782_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2782_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2782_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2782_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2782_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2782_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2782_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2782_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2782_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2782_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all four documents mention \"X-treme Close Up\" and describe it as a video, specifically mentioning that it features vintage concert footage, interviews, and videos. Therefore, the triple \"The type of X-treme Close-Up is a video\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents describe \"X-treme Close Up\" as a video featuring the history, facts, and stories of American hard rock band Kiss. Therefore, it supports the statement that \"The type of X-treme Close-Up is a video.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}